[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "nufcotni - Block of reusable code",
    "answer": "function"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "reterpetni - Runs code line-by-line",
    "answer": "interpreter"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "savelabri - Named data holders",
    "answer": "variables"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "tigreen - Whole number data type",
    "answer": "integer"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "temarapre - Input to a function",
    "answer": "parameter"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "crustt - Custom data grouping",
    "answer": "struct"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "ribylar - Collection of functions",
    "answer": "library"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "tponier - Stores address of a variable",
    "answer": "pointer"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "tnacotsn - Value that cannot be changed",
    "answer": "constant"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "ernurt - Sends a value back from a function",
    "answer": "return"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "ehrdae - Defines structure of functions/data in files",
    "answer": "header"
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "loobena - Logical true/false type in C99",
    "answer": "boolean"
  }
]
